batchbuzz.com 2007-01-17

# BatchBuzz - Privacy Policy

## About BatchBuzz

BatchBuzz is a social networking website for Indian high school and college students. 

## Privacy Policy

We at BatchBuzz are committed to protecting users' privacy. A user's profile information is displayed on the website according to the user’s preferences. The website provides controls to limit access to your profile. 

## Personal Information

Personal information is any piece of information which can potentially be used to uniquely identify, contact, or locate a single person. These include, but are not limited to, a person’s names, telephone numbers and e-mail. 

When you visit BatchBuzz you provide us with personal information you knowingly choose to disclose and website usage information from your interaction with BatchBuzz. We are the sole owner of such information collected on BatchBuzz. We may share statistics and demographic information about members such as interests or occupations but advertisers cannot access your individual personal information. We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process.   

Due to the nature of the internet, we cannot ensure or guarantee the security of any information sent or transmitted to us. Any information that you send or transmit on our website is done purely at your own risk. We advise that users only provide personal information that they are comfortable sharing with strangers.

## Cookies

BatchBuzz may use both session cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them) to provide a customized website experience. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your internet browser help file directions. If you choose to disable cookies, some features of the website may not work properly. Other third parties’ use of their cookies (for advertisements etc) is subject to their own privacy policies. 

## Password

We advise that you keep your password in a safe place, change it frequently and not share accounts with anyone. BatchBuzz will never ask for your password through e-mail or otherwise.

## Third Party Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve advertisements when you visit our website. These companies may use qualified personal information, such as gender or age, and other information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites) in order to provide advertisements on the website about goods and services that may be of interest to you. Our privacy policy does not apply to third parties.

## Updating Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to modify our privacy policy at any time for any reason. We may or may not inform you of updates. We advise that you review this policy frequently. If you object to any changes, you must cease to use our website. Your use of the website and/or registration as a user implies acceptance of the privacy policy.

## Contact Us

BatchBuzz
